import {
  roofing,
  upholstery,
  woodwork,
  woodworkMachines,
  buildingDrawing,
} from "../assets/images";

export default [
  {
    quiz: "Upholstery",
    cover: upholstery,

    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "1. Which of the following would not be found on a bill of materials? ",
        answerA: "Finished size of each wood part",
        answerB: "Rough size of each wood part ",
        answerC: "Fasteners ",
        answerD: "Accessories",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },

      {
        question: "2. A hinge is a piece of hardware used as a ______?",
        answerA: "Joint",
        answerB: "Repair Plate",
        answerC: "Support",
        answerD: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "3. Short pieces of wood can be made into a longer, more usable piece by joining them with ____ joints?",
        answerA: "Surface-lap",
        answerB: "End-to-end half lap",
        answerC: "Cross-lap",
        answerD: "Half-lap",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "4. When using a crosscut saw, which of the following is not recommended? ",
        answerA: "Apply light pressure on the push cuts. ",
        answerB: "Cut with the grain. ",
        answerC: "Cut on the waste side of the cutting line. ",
        answerD: "Hold the saw at a 45-degree angle",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: " 5.Which of the following is used to cut irregular shapes? ",
        answerA: "Backsaw",
        answerB: "Ripsaw",
        answerC: "Dovetail saw",
        answerD: "Compass saw",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Wood Joints",
    cover: woodwork,

    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "1. Butt joints are made by joining together the edge, end, or face surface of one piece of wood to the ____ of another ?",
        answerA: "Edge",
        answerB: "Edge surface",
        answerC: "End",
        answerD: "All of the above",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question:
          "2. The two main types of butt joints include edge butt joints and  ----?",
        answerA: "End butt joints",
        answerB: "Corner butt joints",
        answerC: "Face butt joints",
        answerD: "Angled butt joints",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "3. Butt joints can be strengthened using corner blocks, biscuits, dowels, or ?",
        answerA: "Straps",
        answerB: "Metal fasteners",
        answerC: "Joists",
        answerD: "Tape",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: "4. Biscuits are made from compressed?",
        answerA: "Maple",
        answerB: "Oak",
        answerC: "Beech",
        answerD: "Plywood",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "5. When making biscuit joints, the slots should be slightly longer than the biscuits to allow for?",
        answerA: "Easy removal",
        answerB: "Padding",
        answerC: "Adjustments and expansion",
        answerD: "Compression",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Woodwork Machines",
    cover: woodworkMachines,

    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "1.	Which of the following is not a helper used to feed stock into a tool?",
        answerA: "Push-stick",
        answerB: "Feather-board",
        answerC: "Push-block",
        answerD: "Straightedge",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question:
          "2.	Which type of gloves should be worn when working with sharp edges and rough materials? ",
        answerA: "Plastic",
        answerB: "Lightweight cotton",
        answerC: "Leather or thick fabric",
        answerD: "Rubber",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "3.	The size of a power drill is determined by the size of its ?",
        answerA: "Bit",
        answerB: "Chuck",
        answerC: "Torque",
        answerD: "Collar",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "4. A hand drill is generally used to drill holes ____ or less in diameter?",

        answerA: "¼ Inch ",
        answerB: "¾ inch ",
        answerC: "1/8 inch ",
        answerD: "A of the above",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question: "5.	On some power drills, a chuck key is used to ?",
        answerA: "Tighten the jaws around the bit.",
        answerB: "Loosen screws that are too tight. ",
        answerC: "Lock the drill for safety reasons. 	",
        answerD: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Building Drawing",
    cover: buildingDrawing,

    questions: [
      {
        question: "1.	This type of section is limited by a break line ?",
        answerA: "Removed section",
        answerB: "Resolved section",
        answerC: "Broken-out section",
        answerD: "Half section",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "2.	Drafters should use a ________ in a section view of a mechanical part that includes the cylindrical view of a threaded hole?",
        answerA: "Center line",
        answerB: "Hatch line",
        answerC: "Poly line",
        answerD: "Dimension line",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "3.	The section view drawing in which one fourth of an object has been marked for removal is known as a ________ section ?",
        answerA: "Full",
        answerB: "Half",
        answerC: "Quarter",
        answerD: "None of the above",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "4.	In offset sections, offsets or bends in the cutting plane are all?",
        answerA: "90 degrees",
        answerB: "180 degrees",
        answerC: "Either 90 or 180 degrees",
        answerD: "30, 60,90 degrees",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "5.	This type of solid is egg-shaped and can be created by revolving an ellipse around one of its axes ?",
        answerA: "Ellipsoid",
        answerB: "Torus",
        answerC: "Cone",
        answerD: "Cylinder",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Roofing",
    cover: roofing,

    questions: [
      {
        question: "1.	Which of the following is not a softwood ?",
        answerA: "Pine",
        answerB: "Redwood",
        answerC: "Birch",
        answerD: "Cedar",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question: "2.	Which of the following is not a hardwood ?",
        answerA: "Fir",
        answerB: "Maple ",
        answerC: "Walnut",
        answerD: "Cherry",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question: "3. The first step in lumber processing is called ?",
        answerA: "Selective cutting",
        answerB: "baking",
        answerC: "Air drying",
        answerD: "Kiln drying",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "4. When making a miter cut, adjust the ____ to the angle desired ?",
        answerA: "Table",
        answerB: "Blade guard",
        answerC: "Overarm",
        answerD: "Column",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question: "5.	To cut a bevel, adjust the track for ?",
        answerA: "Ripping",
        answerB: "Straight crosscutting",
        answerC: "Duplicate parts",
        answerD: "Duplicate parts",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
    ],
  },
];
